freemmogamer.com 2016-10-02

# Privacy Policy - FreeMMOGamer

## GENERAL

Your privacy is important to us. Our Privacy Policy describes our practices concerning data that you provide or that we may collect about you through the Services, and you consent to our use of data in compliance with the Privacy Policy.

## COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

FreeMMOGamer.com does not sell, exchange, or release your personal information without your consent to any third parties.

## USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

We use Personal Information for our own internal purposes including contacting you via email to inform you about updates to Site. We reserve the right to disclose your information as required by law. We do not rent or sell our Users’ Personal Information to third parties. We do, however, provide you with the opportunity to receive newsletters via email. If you decide to opt in to receive newsletters, you may opt out of receiving these newsletters at any time. We use your IP address and browser information to help diagnose problems with our server and to gather broad demographic information.

## COOKIES

Cookies are small data files that a website you visit may save on your computer or handheld device that usually includes an anonymous unique identifier. Our Website may use cookies for user authentication, tracking our audience size and traffic patterns.

Information gathered through the use of cookies is not related to any personally identifiable details. Many browsers are set to accept cookies. You may prefer to set your browser to refuse cookies. It is possible, however, that some areas of the site will not function properly if you do so.

Third-party advertisers may also create and access cookies, which will be subject to their privacy policies – we accept no responsibility or liability for the use of such third parties’ cookies.

## POLICY CHANGES

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice. You are advised to check our Website regularly to view our most recent privacy policy.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy please email our team at contact@freemmogamer.com
